<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>AWS Public Sector on Internship Report</title><link>https://phatpham14.github.io/fcj-fa25/tags/aws-public-sector/</link><description>Recent content in AWS Public Sector on Internship Report</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://phatpham14.github.io/fcj-fa25/tags/aws-public-sector/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Proactive Strategies for Cyber Resilience and Business Continuity on AWS</title><link>https://phatpham14.github.io/fcj-fa25/3-blogstranslated/3.3-blog3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://phatpham14.github.io/fcj-fa25/3-blogstranslated/3.3-blog3/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>By Devin Gordon and Henrik Balle&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img alt="pic 1" src="../../images/3-Blog/B3-1.png">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/">Amazon Web Services (AWS)&lt;/a> recommends that organizations prepare to recover workloads in the event of cybersecurity incidents or business continuity events such as natural disasters or technical failures. In this post, we provide guidance and strategies for Public Sector organizations to use AWS infrastructure to operate resilient systems in the cloud.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>AWS recommends that its customers:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Use cybersecurity frameworks and AWS architectural best practices.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Implement a multi-account environment.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Use &lt;a href="https://aws.amazon.com/what-is/iac/">infrastructure as code (IaC)&lt;/a> to deploy AWS environments and workloads.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Prepare a recovery account in an Availability Zone or &lt;a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/glossary/latest/reference/glos-chap.html#region">Region&lt;/a> different from the primary workload.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Include all application code, IaC code, configuration files, and other dependencies in the recovery account.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Define a data backup strategy to the recovery account.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Implement automated testing (unit and full workload) in the recovery account.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="use-an-established-framework">Use an established framework&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>As cybersecurity incidents like ransomware increase, Public Sector organizations look to frameworks such as the &lt;a href="https://www.nist.gov/cyberframework">NIST Cybersecurity Framework (CSF) 2.0&lt;/a> from the &lt;a href="https://www.nist.gov/">National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)&lt;/a> to guide better cybersecurity risk governance. While the CSF organizes cybersecurity outcomes by functions (govern, identify, protect, detect, respond, recover), NIST does not prescribe specific ways to achieve those outcomes.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>